One, two! One, two, three!
- Guidance system?
- Online.
- Autopilot?
- Present.
- Dark matter indicator?
- Making a noise.
All systems operational. Let's rock.
Gentlemen, I've completed
my report on the crash.
Whoa! I'm not readin' that crap!
Summarize it in one word.
Sabotage.
This is a normal L-unit. Without it,
space travel is but
the fevered dream of a madman.
- Yeah.
- Of course!
- It's an important unit.
- And this, my friends,
is the L-unit I just
removed from the ship.
That doesn't look like an "L"
at all, unless you count lowercase.
- You know we don't!
- Ooh!
Whoever did this was strong.
This is 340 pounds of Tonka-tough steel.
Mmm... It should look like this...
But instead it looks like this.
- Who would do a thing like that?
- Who could do a thing like that?
And by "that," I mean this.
Well, gang, it looks like we have
another mystery on our hands.
I'd better make a chart of the suspects.
I'll begin by drawing a line
with my straightedge.
Sweet lamprey of Santa Fe!
My edge has been bent!
My javelin, too! It's ruined!
Now we'll never beat Jupiter State.
My Slinky! My cuddly little pet Slinky!
What's all the hubbub?
My God! Even the professor's been bent!
Thank you for your sympathy,
talking square of linoleum.
I'll get you fixed up.
That's fine.
Wait a minute! Bender,
what did you just do to the professor?
I bent him.
- It's Bender!
- J'accusé.
Oh, I see, a bunch of stuff gets bent,
so it must be the robot
designed for bending.
I know how to settle this.
We'll check last night's
surveillance tapes.
- Surveillance?
- What tapes?
You've seen me naked?
Ah, last night's tape. It was right next
to Bathroom Bloopers Four.
See? Nothin'. Told you, losers!
Wait. There on the screen.
It's that guy you are!
I'm sleepwalkin'.
Dear Lord, we've got robots
on the ceiling!
You weren't sleepwalking.
You were sleep-bending.
This is quite a shock!
On the other hand,
it's not surprising in the least.
After all, I've been bending
since the day I was built.
I was born on an assembly line
in the bad part of Tijuana.
Mama.
Hooray! I graduated!
Time to bend around Europe
for a few months,
then get a job bending.
You remember your own birth?
Sure. It was only four years ago.
- You're only four years old?
- Precocious little scamp, ain't I?
Bender must have a pent-up need to bend
that's not being satisfied
by his bend-free lifestyle.
Then he can't stay here.
He's a menace to every
straight person in the company.
Go satisfy your bend lust,
and don't you come back
to work until you do!
No more bending! No more work!
Give us a raise, you big fat jerk!
Nevers!
Yo! The mafia supports ya!
But don't tell no one. Spread the word.
As the duly elected mobsters
of this union,
it's our duty to support the struggle
of these proud, lazy slobs.
Yeah, but what if management
remains "intragnizent"?
From the context,
it is clear what you mean.
In that case, Clamps may have
a little surprise for them.
The clamps! Right?
Ah, no. A strike?
Now I'll never get to bend anything!
- Oh, woe is Bender!
- Hang tough, brother.
Management refused our demand
to switch casual Friday to Monday.
- What?
- And now they're hiring scabs
at 10 times the normal wage.
Ten times normal wage!
I'll give those jerks what for!
- Welcomes aboard, scab.
- Great to be here.
Come on. I'll introduces you
to your scab coworkers
you'll be scabbin' with.
This here's our scab foreman.
- Flexo?
- Bender?
Hey, sorry you got sent to that
South American Turkish prison
instead of me
on account of mistaken identity.
You bastard!
They treated me like an animal!
And that's what I became!
Nah, you're all right.
Good to see ya, buddy.
And here's another scab
what also works here.
Angelyne.
Hello!
Hey! Youse guyses wanna move that thing?
Give us a raise, you big fat jerk!
Nevers!
Ow!
Um, hi, Angelyne. Whatcha up to?
Makin' hangers. Guidance counselor
said I had a knack for it.
That's cool. That's cool.
So, um... Uh...
I was wonderin' if,
you know, it's cool if not...
But what are you doin' after work?
What I always do. Jack squat.
Me, too.
Man, we have a lot in common, huh?
Well, we are made of
virtually identical components.
Are you sure?
Maybe I should sneak a peak
at your access panel.
Hey, according to the Scab Handbook,
that's extremely inappropriate banter.
And that's just the way I like it.
Haile H. Selassie!
There, little friend. Good as new.
What an exquisite day!
That azure sky. The verdant treetops.
Those delightful birds
with their chirp, chirp, chirp
and their tweet, tweet, splat.
Professor, I've never
seen you so cheerful.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- Hmm...
I'm not quite sure.
Perhaps seeing things
from a new perspective
has reminded me of life's beauty.
Or perhaps my new posture is causing blood
to pool in the back of my brain,
resulting in a mild delirium.
Incidentally, you have
a dime up your nose.
I wish. It's a nickel.
Union forever!
Lousy scabs!
They can't do those things! Et cetera!
I bet watchin' me bend girders
like this turns your legs all rubbery.
Well, my legs are made of rubber.
And anyway, I am just
as strong as you are, Mac.
Oh, yeah? Prove it.
Here, let me help you.
Bend me, shape me
any way you want me
Long as you love me, it's all right
Bend me, shape me
any way you want me
You got the power to turn on the light
Bend me, shape me
any way you want me
Long as you love me, it's all right
Bend me, shape me
any way you want me
Long as you love me, it's all right
Bend me, shape me
any way you want me
My new bent outlook
has completely re-energized me.
I'm even dating a young
Brazilian retired actress.
- Way to go!
- Great!
Some say I'm robbing the cradle,
but I say she's robbing the grave.
Howdy, doodies! What's new?
I was just regaling your former co-workers
with a tale of bedroom antics
the likes of which...
Yeah, yeah, big whoop. No one cares.
I got Bender-related news. I'm in love.
And I'm takin' all my friends
out to celebrate.
Let's go live it up!
Hey, look at this crowd.
You guys gotta try the pasta.
It's got a real nice profit margin.
Bam! So, special occasion tonight?
Oh, Elzar, you'll never guess
what's happened!
- Bam?
- I've met the most dynamite ladybot.
Hey, that's terrific.
To celebrate,
I'm gonna stick seven copies
of my latest cookbook on your bill.
Bless you, sir.
So, Bender, tell us about
this new girlfriend of yours.
I intend to,
through the lost art of the toast.
To Angelyne, she's got it all.
Looks, charm and the love
of a fabulous bending robot.
She sure does.
Flexo!
Careful! That's a week old!
I finally meet a nice girl,
with a pair of legs
that don't quit unexpectedly,
and that jerk Flexo steals her away?
It's time to kick some shiny metal ass!
You degenerate hussy!
I'm disappointed in you too, Angelyne.
Bender,
it's not what you think.
Oh, God, then it's worse than I think!
Now look, there is no reason to be upset.
- Flexo and I are divorced.
- Huh?
We're just havin' dinner
'cause we wanna stay friends.
I knew that.
What I'm actually outraged by
is your choice of wine!
Really, it's the steward's fault.
Excellent choice, sir.
That Flexo! Why,
I'm knockin' him right on his butt.
Can't believe this.
Obsessing won't help, Bender.
Take a lean back and enjoy life.
I can't. My fembot may be
in love with another manbot.
Well, talk to her.
Tell her about your feelings
in an open and honest way.
Yeah. Either that or be a man.
Okay, I've constructed
an elaborate lie.
I'll call Angelyne
while pretending to be Flexo,
arrange a date, show up disguised as him
and catch her two-timing me with myself.
That's thinkin' like a man.
Hello? This is Flexo.
Now we'll see who loves whom.
- Hey, hot stuff.
- Hey, Flexo.
So since when do you go to bars
on work nights?
It's not like you at all.
Nonsense. It's exactly like me.
Flexo, the fun-lovin' love machine
fembots love to love.
Hey, barkeep, I'll have a fuzzy navel,
and she'll have
the girliest drink in the house.
Two fuzzy navels comin' up.
I hope they can make change for a fortune.
Yo, get an eyeload of that
filthy scab with the beard
flashin' his filthy scab money.
- It's an insult to you, boss.
- Yeah.
That cash ought to be slushin' my fund
and kicks-in' my back.
I'm greasin' up my whoozits.
Whoa, whoa. Clamps. Not yet.
Let's just keep an eye on him
and see if he does it a couple more times.
You're looking good to Flexo tonight.
Quit makin' with the googly eyes.
You know that I'm in love with Bender.
Bender? That walkin' wuss factory?
He may be a walkin' factory,
but believe me, he is no wuss.
Now look, you and me are through.
I told you that when I divorced you.
But goin' through a divorce together,
you can't tell me
that didn't bring us closer.
Care to dance?
Well, you know I love dancin',
but you always hated it.
In that case, it's somethin' I've always
wanted to make up to you.
Hey, Scratchmo!
How about droppin' me and the lady
some rump-rattlin' beats?
I had hoped by the second time
he flashed his cash,
my rage would've subsided.
Sadly, that has not happened.
You used to be so inflexible, Flexo.
You have really loosened up.
I recently upgraded my funk card.
Argh. Come on!
- All right!
- Come on, now!
What's new?
Flexo? What's goin' on?
Did... Um...
Oh!
Flexo!
So the moral of the story is,
if you want it to stay sunk,
tie a weight to it!
You know, you always were
a kick in the teeth, man.
Aw, shucks, thunder buns.
You make me feel like a million volts.
Oh, Flexo, Flexo, Flexo.
I'm startin' to remember
why I fell for you in the first place.
So, she's fallin' for Flexo, eh?
I'd better seduce her
a little more, just to be sure.
Well, it's late.
I should get home to my trailer.
I'll walk you out.
After all, a true gentlemen
tends to his date's every need.
Tiparillo?
Here you are, my lad.
Bring the lady's car around
in the finest way possible.
He's flashin' his cash loaf again.
How many times is that?
- Two or three?
- Three.
All right. That's the necessary
number of times.
That scab's gonna have a little
on-the-job accident.
With all due respect, Donbot,
I don't think we should rely
on an accident happenin'.
Let's kill him ourselves.
Well, good night. I had a great time.
How about a lift to your place?
- What?
- Admit it.
You felt somethin' for me tonight.
And by "me," I mean Flexo.
Hey, look, I had fun, but...
- But?
- But...
But?
But...
Huh? Bender! You tricked me!
That's right, baby!
I ain't your lover boy Flexo,
the guy you love so much!
You even love anybody
pretending to be him!
Well, maybe I love you so much,
I love you no matter
who you're pretending to be.
Oh, how I wish I could believe
or understand that!
There's only one reasonable
course of action now.
Kill Flexo!
Ow!
No!
Thanks. I appreciate that.
Nah, I'm joshin' ya.
That was quite annoying.
You call yourself divorced?
You're makin' a mockery of one
of our oldest institutions!
What?
All right, boss. Give the word,
and I'll drop this unbendable girder,
clamp, clamp, ca-bamp!
Remember, only kill
the one with the beard.
That other filthy scab,
we got nothin' against.
- That's low!
- Please stop! I'm not worth it!
Probably not, but I love you,
and I'm gonna kick his ass
till I win you back!
Hey!
Okay, Clamps, now.
Ahhh!
Ooh, that's gotta clamp!
Flexo, are you okay?
Yeah. Never better.
Nah, I'm yankin' your chain. I'm dyin'.
You can't die! Tonight Bender
showed me that I love you.
But... I love you.
I know, and I care for you, too.
But I could never love anyone
as much as you made me realize
I love Flexo!
But... But...
I love you so much, Angelyne,
I want you to be happy, no matter what.
But what are you sayin'?
I'm sayin' I've got
an unbendable girder to bend.
You can't bend that girder.
It's unbendable!
Well, I don't know anything about lifting,
so that just leaves us the one option.
Thanks, buddy.
Another year under that,
and I'd have been a goner.
I'll always
remember this, Bender.
Me, too. Me, too.
Jerk.
So, Flexo and Angelyne had sex
right there on the factory floor?
Well, at least you got
bending out of your system.
Yes. I won't be up to bending
again for a long, long time.
Perhaps it's your outlook
that needs a good bend,
a 90-degree bend
to a place where happiness
is perpendicular to wonderment.
Professor, we're all sick
of your upbeat attitude.
- I'll say.
- Believe it.
Nonsense. It's just like
in the song I wrote.
We all need
a new angle on life...
Bender, you've gotta help us.
I try to get out,
but they keep pullin' me back in!
Wangle a new dangle on life
No, Bender! The other way!
I like him better this way.
I'm sad now.
Eh, it's fine.